{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083423451","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083423450"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 9f461528-943f-4bb3-be50-0d67fb2f50c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_vo_vo-po-to"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083433728","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083433728"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 66ff22ce-c289-4b62-ba49-b058389226bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_mche-ta-mpi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083438663","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083438663"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 66ff22ce-c289-4b62-ba49-b058389226bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ku-ta-nyi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083443684","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083443684"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 66ff22ce-c289-4b62-ba49-b058389226bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ng'u-fo-ta"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083464358","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083464358"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 66ff22ce-c289-4b62-ba49-b058389226bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ng'i-ta-mwa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083473406","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083473406"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 66ff22ce-c289-4b62-ba49-b058389226bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ta-vyi-ve"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083487405","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083487404"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 66ff22ce-c289-4b62-ba49-b058389226bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_si-ta-shu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083493359","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083493359"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 66ff22ce-c289-4b62-ba49-b058389226bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_do-ta-mo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083501096","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083501095"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 66ff22ce-c289-4b62-ba49-b058389226bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ta-pe-ngu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083505928","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083505928"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 66ff22ce-c289-4b62-ba49-b058389226bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_mwu-ta-shi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083510565","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083510565"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 66ff22ce-c289-4b62-ba49-b058389226bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ti-ta-mwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083516318","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083516317"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 66ff22ce-c289-4b62-ba49-b058389226bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ti-ta-mwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083525898","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083525898"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 66ff22ce-c289-4b62-ba49-b058389226bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ti-ta-mwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083531451","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083531451"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 66ff22ce-c289-4b62-ba49-b058389226bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ti-ta-mwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083541450","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083541450"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 66ff22ce-c289-4b62-ba49-b058389226bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ti-ta-mwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083547821","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083547820"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 6dcb73dc-2c66-44f6-8bc1-722a287b9fe7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083549174","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083549174"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 6dcb73dc-2c66-44f6-8bc1-722a287b9fe7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083549254","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083549253"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 6dcb73dc-2c66-44f6-8bc1-722a287b9fe7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083559449","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083559448"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" ae12f1c0-ec8f-497f-a890-61d3f4d178f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ji_je-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083563963","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083563963"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" ae12f1c0-ec8f-497f-a890-61d3f4d178f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jo_di-jo-wi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jo"," userResponse":" jo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083595974","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083595974"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" ae12f1c0-ec8f-497f-a890-61d3f4d178f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wu_zo-wu-ja"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wu"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083924194","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083924194"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" ae12f1c0-ec8f-497f-a890-61d3f4d178f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wu_zo-wu-ja"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wu"," userResponse":" wu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083929074","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083929074"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" ae12f1c0-ec8f-497f-a890-61d3f4d178f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_de_pe-ha-de"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" de"," userResponse":" de"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083933612","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083933611"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" ae12f1c0-ec8f-497f-a890-61d3f4d178f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ga_pe-ti-ga"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083938336","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083938336"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" ae12f1c0-ec8f-497f-a890-61d3f4d178f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ze_ku-wa-ze"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ze"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083944481","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083944481"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" ae12f1c0-ec8f-497f-a890-61d3f4d178f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ze_ku-wa-ze"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ze"," userResponse":" ze"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083948622","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083948622"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" ae12f1c0-ec8f-497f-a890-61d3f4d178f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-no-da"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083952806","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083952806"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" ae12f1c0-ec8f-497f-a890-61d3f4d178f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ho_ho-sa-mu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ho"," userResponse":" ho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083957548","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083957548"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" ae12f1c0-ec8f-497f-a890-61d3f4d178f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_du-pu-ta"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083963363","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083963362"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" ae12f1c0-ec8f-497f-a890-61d3f4d178f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pi_pi-zo-we"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083969132","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083969132"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" ae12f1c0-ec8f-497f-a890-61d3f4d178f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_pi_pi-zo-we"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083977334","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083977333"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" ae12f1c0-ec8f-497f-a890-61d3f4d178f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_pi_pi-zo-we"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083990472","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083990472"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 6086b213-d435-4065-b531-4faab53655c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fa_fa-ra-sa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" fa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083995071","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083995071"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 6086b213-d435-4065-b531-4faab53655c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ri_ri-fi-si"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549083999743","data":{"timestamp":" 1549083999743"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 6086b213-d435-4065-b531-4faab53655c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vo_vo-po-to"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vo"," userResponse":" vo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084004114","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084004114"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 6086b213-d435-4065-b531-4faab53655c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bu_bu-zu-fu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084008281","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084008281"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 6086b213-d435-4065-b531-4faab53655c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-to-vo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084022222","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084022222"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 6086b213-d435-4065-b531-4faab53655c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-lo-po"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084027745","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084027745"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 6086b213-d435-4065-b531-4faab53655c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mo_mo-ko-ro"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mo"," userResponse":" mo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084032274","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084032274"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 6086b213-d435-4065-b531-4faab53655c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_pu-ru-lu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084037554","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084037554"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 6086b213-d435-4065-b531-4faab53655c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_le-me-re"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084041783","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084041783"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 6086b213-d435-4065-b531-4faab53655c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_li_li-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084047535","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084047534"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 6086b213-d435-4065-b531-4faab53655c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_li_li-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084053868","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084053868"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 6086b213-d435-4065-b531-4faab53655c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_li_li-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084074018","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084074018"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 2bf17bb5-c3c1-421e-acdf-8c8361294a43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mfa_vu_nzi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084080689","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084080688"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 2bf17bb5-c3c1-421e-acdf-8c8361294a43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_gha_vu_mba"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084087372","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084087372"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 2bf17bb5-c3c1-421e-acdf-8c8361294a43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_wa_vu_nchi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084094036","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084094036"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 2bf17bb5-c3c1-421e-acdf-8c8361294a43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_vu_ye_ngu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084100698","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084100697"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 2bf17bb5-c3c1-421e-acdf-8c8361294a43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_vu_nji_mwe"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084107344","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084107344"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 2bf17bb5-c3c1-421e-acdf-8c8361294a43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mu_fu_vu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084113996","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084113996"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 2bf17bb5-c3c1-421e-acdf-8c8361294a43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mle_vu_vyi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084120656","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084120655"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 2bf17bb5-c3c1-421e-acdf-8c8361294a43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_pi_vyi_vu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084127299","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084127299"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 2bf17bb5-c3c1-421e-acdf-8c8361294a43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_vu_shu_vya"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084133984","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084133984"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 2bf17bb5-c3c1-421e-acdf-8c8361294a43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ze_mbu_vu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084147064","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084147064"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 2bf17bb5-c3c1-421e-acdf-8c8361294a43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.vu..vu.noShow..5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_ze_mbu_vu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084156286","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084156286"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" bf55b84f-2ea2-4a7f-a911-b1ec53e49c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084156511","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084156511"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" bf55b84f-2ea2-4a7f-a911-b1ec53e49c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084157475","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084157474"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" bf55b84f-2ea2-4a7f-a911-b1ec53e49c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084158748","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084158748"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" bf55b84f-2ea2-4a7f-a911-b1ec53e49c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084159319","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084159319"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" bf55b84f-2ea2-4a7f-a911-b1ec53e49c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084159429","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084159429"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" bf55b84f-2ea2-4a7f-a911-b1ec53e49c2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084170740","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084170739"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 7d6e3ef8-d53d-47ae-b64c-0bcf46cece52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" va"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VA"," userResponse":" VA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084173776","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084173776"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 7d6e3ef8-d53d-47ae-b64c-0bcf46cece52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" va"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084175317","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084175317"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 7d6e3ef8-d53d-47ae-b64c-0bcf46cece52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ve"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VE"," userResponse":" VE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084178465","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084178465"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 7d6e3ef8-d53d-47ae-b64c-0bcf46cece52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ve"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084180026","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084180025"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 7d6e3ef8-d53d-47ae-b64c-0bcf46cece52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VI"," userResponse":" VI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084183215","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084183215"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 7d6e3ef8-d53d-47ae-b64c-0bcf46cece52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084184766","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084184766"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 7d6e3ef8-d53d-47ae-b64c-0bcf46cece52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VO"," userResponse":" VO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084187656","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084187656"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 7d6e3ef8-d53d-47ae-b64c-0bcf46cece52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084189214","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084189214"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 7d6e3ef8-d53d-47ae-b64c-0bcf46cece52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VU"," userResponse":" VU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084192340","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084192340"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 7d6e3ef8-d53d-47ae-b64c-0bcf46cece52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084194354","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084194353"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 7d6e3ef8-d53d-47ae-b64c-0bcf46cece52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" vu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084194524","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084194524"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 7d6e3ef8-d53d-47ae-b64c-0bcf46cece52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084205683","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084205683"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 7d6e3ef8-d53d-47ae-b64c-0bcf46cece52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" vu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084216398","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084216398"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 7d6e3ef8-d53d-47ae-b64c-0bcf46cece52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" vu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084223773","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084223773"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 7d6e3ef8-d53d-47ae-b64c-0bcf46cece52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" vu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084234742","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084234742"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 7d6e3ef8-d53d-47ae-b64c-0bcf46cece52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" vu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084241755","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084241754"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 4f2fa1c5-0e16-4ba6-8ada-49e0f139dc22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084244058","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084244058"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 4f2fa1c5-0e16-4ba6-8ada-49e0f139dc22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084244123","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084244122"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 4f2fa1c5-0e16-4ba6-8ada-49e0f139dc22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084254029","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084254029"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 4f2fa1c5-0e16-4ba6-8ada-49e0f139dc22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084260916","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084260916"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 4f2fa1c5-0e16-4ba6-8ada-49e0f139dc22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084271424","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084271424"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 89483b4c-6ba9-4d20-afa4-3c722deaf1f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bu_bu-zu-fu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084276258","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084276257"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 89483b4c-6ba9-4d20-afa4-3c722deaf1f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_le-me-re"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084280424","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084280424"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 89483b4c-6ba9-4d20-afa4-3c722deaf1f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_pu-ru-lu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084284514","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084284514"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 89483b4c-6ba9-4d20-afa4-3c722deaf1f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-lo-po"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084288700","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084288700"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 89483b4c-6ba9-4d20-afa4-3c722deaf1f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vo_vo-po-to"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vo"," userResponse":" vo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084292627","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084292627"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 89483b4c-6ba9-4d20-afa4-3c722deaf1f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ri_ri-fi-si"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084296630","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084296629"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 89483b4c-6ba9-4d20-afa4-3c722deaf1f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fa_fa-ra-sa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" fa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084300766","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084300766"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 89483b4c-6ba9-4d20-afa4-3c722deaf1f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-to-vo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084304899","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084304899"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 89483b4c-6ba9-4d20-afa4-3c722deaf1f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mo_mo-ko-ro"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mo"," userResponse":" mo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084308912","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084308912"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 89483b4c-6ba9-4d20-afa4-3c722deaf1f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_li_li-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549084314679","data":{"timestamp":" 1549084314679"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_075655"," gameId":" 89483b4c-6ba9-4d20-afa4-3c722deaf1f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_li_li-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}